In the last lesson we talked about different phrases we can use when we're picking somebody up at the
在上一课中，我们讨论了在接人时可以使用的不同短语
airport.
飞机场。
Very important social situation in this lesson we're going to talk about how to describe data in graphs.
本课中非常重要的社会情境，我们将讨论如何用图表来描述数据。
So usually when we express or want to show a large amount of data which means information and communicate
所以通常当我们表达或想要展示大量数据时，意味着信息和交流
that to someone we don't just say all of the different numbers or all of the different facts that we
对某人，我们不只是说出我们所有不同的数字或所有不同的事实
want to say we represent it or show it in a graph or a chart or some type of we could say visualization
想说我们表示它或以图形或图表或某种类型的方式显示它，我们可以说是可视化
visualization is a way to show something in a way that people can see right.
可视化是一种以人们可以正确看到的方式展示事物的方式。
So that people can easily understand it.
让人们很容易理解它。
Maybe they can understand it in a more intuitive way.
也许他们可以用更直观的方式理解它。
Well let's say you're in a meeting and you want to communicate what you're seeing in a chart or a graph
好吧，假设您正在开会，并且想要传达您在图表或图形中看到的内容
because maybe there's somebody on the phone.
因为也许有人在打电话。
It's important to be able to express information simply and say what you're looking at.
能够简单地表达信息并说出你在看什么是很重要的。
Now we've we've worked on that early in this course.
现在我们已经在本课程的早期进行了研究。
We talked about for example the House.
我们谈到了例如房子。
So we described that.
所以我们描述了这一点。
But what about when it's a graph.
但是当它是一个图表时呢？
Well in this lesson we're going to be focused on how we can do that how we can express what we're looking
那么在本课中，我们将专注于如何做到这一点，如何表达我们正在寻找的东西
at a data visualization.
在数据可视化中。
Now this may sound very difficult.
现在这听起来可能非常困难。
The best way I think for me to show you a way to do this is to do an example.
我认为向您展示这样做的最佳方法是举一个例子。
So what we're going to do is we're going to look at a look at a graph and we're going to then talk about
所以我们要做的就是看一下图表，然后我们将讨论
what it means.
这是什么意思。
First we're gonna go through some keywords some useful some useful words then we're going to actually
首先，我们将通过一些关键字一些有用的一些有用的词然后我们将实际
look at the graph and we're going to talk about how we can describe what's going on there.
看一下图表，我们将讨论如何描述那里发生的事情。
I'm going to give you a clear example.
我要给你一个明确的例子。
Then we'll go over a few phrases we can use to express an analysis of that what it means really if we
然后我们将回顾一些可以用来表达分析的短语，如果我们
start asking deeper questions.
开始问更深层次的问题。 现在这部分实际上是更具挑战性的部分，但我认为越多越有趣。
So let's get started with some of the vocabulary and then we will look at the graph.
因此，让我们从一些词汇表开始，然后我们将查看图表。